Ms. Yuki!
How may I assist you?
Oh, uh... There's something
I need your help with.
"Something"?
It's this.
Um...
I know it's kind of a cliché to reinvent your
image during summer vacation, but...
I've been wanting to get my ears pierced
ever since my friend did!
But I don't have the guts to
pierce them myself, so...
I was wondering if you could do it for me.
You would like me to?
I noticed your ears are pierced, too,
so I was thinking it'd be safer to have
someone with experience do it, you know?
Understood.
Thanks!
Now, do me a favor and pierce them
with one swift blow!
Ms. Yuki?
I-Is this some sort of hazing ritual
for new employees?
Have I failed you in some way?
What?!
My apologies!
I couldn't possibly do something as horrible
as opening a hole in your flesh,
Master Hitoyoshi!
Uh, didn't you used to put holes
in people for a living?
Um, Ms. Yuki...
Big Brother
I adopted a dog.
Pup, pup, puppy!
I wonder what it's like...
Is it lively?
Is it shy?
Oh!
Big Brother! Show me the puppy!
Would you happen to be
Master Hitoyoshi's little sister?
Episode 3: You are Ms. Yuki.
Whoa!
The house is so clean!
The puppy is so fluffy!
And on top of that...
I had no idea there was
such a beautiful maid here!
Why didn't you tell me about her?!
Doh puhl mah cheechz!
We've been texting all the time,
but you haven't mentioned her once!
Well, I didn't want to risk Mom finding out
and getting worried, for one thing.
What did you say to Dad?
I asked if I could hire a new housekeeper.
He okayed it over the phone as always.
I don't know whether Dad trusts you
or just neglects you...
Wait! That's not the issue here!
How could you keep your little sister
in the dark like this?
That's unforgivable behavior, you know?
Do you both reside in separate houses?
Y-Yes.
U-Um...
Oh!
It's just... You're so beautiful,
I can't believe it!
Riko just loves beautiful people.
That's why I didn't want to tell her.
I knew she'd be annoying about it.
Doh putt youh fingers in mah mouse!
Big Brother, you jerk!
How could you keep her all to yourself?!
Oh, I forgot to introduce myself!
I'm Riko,
younger sister to my fool
of an older brother here.
Nice to meet ya!
Don't just slide in an insult.
They say I'm a clever kid! Keep that
in mind when you Riko-ll my name!
So what's your name, Miss?
I'm... Yuki.
My name is Yuki.
What a wonderful name!
It is!
Master Hitoyoshi was kind
enough to give it to me.
Oh?
And here I thought Big Brother
had no naming ability whatsoever.
Wait, he gave it to you?
Indeed. I was formerly an assassin, and...
Ms. Yuki, wait!
...as I did not have a specific name,
I asked him to grant me one.
For real.
That's so... so...
wonderful!
Phew...
You're beautiful and strong... It's perfect!
May I have your autograph?
My autograph...?
All you have to do is write
your name down here.
Riko-chan's Clever Notebook
8th Edition
Come on! Come on! Please!
If that is your wish, I shall write it.
She looks picture-perfect just sitting there...
She's more like an upper-class lady
than an assassin!
I've finished.
Thank you!
Yuki
Will this do?
Huh?
Not exactly what I had in mind...
Oh! Is it not to your liking?
Oh, no, it's nothing like that!
I was just noticing your unique handwriting.
Spoken communication is my strong point.
In fact, I speak around twelve languages.
Wow, Ms. Global!
I was sent all around the world
for my job, you see.
So cool!
However, I was never taught calligraphy,
so I must apologize for showing you
something so unsightly.
It's okay. This is cute in its own way,
since it looks like an idol's autograph.
If so, I'm glad.
Oh! I thought of a great idea!
Great idea?
Yep! For this year's summer vacation
research assignment, my subject will be...
Ms. Yuki!
You've already made up your mind, huh?
Is that okay?!
If you are okay with one such as me.
You're the only one for me, Ms. Yuki!
Now, then...
Show me your killer moves!
What?
Riko! Don't write anything
weird for school, okay?
Perish the thought!
I'll be writing a killer diary of my killer
notes on a beautiful maid's killer skills!
What? Are you sure that's going to be okay?
Miss Riko.
Please step out into the yard, if you would.
Roger dodger!
Whoa... Wow!
All right, here I go.
Amazing!
Wow!
Hey, Ms. Yuki! Where did you
pull that knife from just now?
From my breast pocket.
How many do you have?
Where do you keep them?!
I originally carried sixteen.
Sixteen?!
However, I was told that it was
too many by Master Hitoyoshi,
and so I carry five now.
Where are those five?
One is in my breast pocket,
and as for the rest...
I have two attached to each leg
via garters, for five in total.
Wait, wait, wait!
Stop!
Wow, what a cute bell!
Thank you very much.
But doesn't it interfere with your work?
By the time my target hears the bell,
I have already dealt the killing blow.
So cool!
I want to try saying that!
"By the time my target hears the bell..."
Everyone totally heard
your stomach growling, Riko.
Well, I can't do anything
about that! I'm hungry!
Okay, okay.
Well, it is lunch time.
Why don't we make something?
I know!
What's your specialty dish, Ms. Yuki?
What?
I'm not sure if I can call it a dish, but...
That's just what I want to see!
Isn't this where...
you'd go all "whoosh" with the knife?
Yes, but I've come to realize that this
is the most efficient way to cut it.
Amazing!
Well, I guess cabbage on its own
doesn't make a meal.
We can probably eat it with something tonight.
Oh.
Katsuda Fireworks Festival
Time: 19:30-20:15
Summer Festival
Hey, today is the summer festival!
I wanna go!
Let's go!
They have a certain something there
you'll like, Ms. Yuki.
What do you mean?
Katsuda's Sauce
A stall for senbei crackers
served with that sauce.
Sauce... Senbei...
U-Um, Master Hitoyoshi...
Fine by me. Let's go.
Katsuda Fireworks Festival
Time: 19:30-20:15
Summer Festival
Then it's decided!
Summer festival, here we come!
Shaved Ice
Yakisoba
Takoyaki
It's looking fun already!
Now, then!
All right!
Charge!
Shooting Gallery
Sh-Shooting... is not my forte.
Wow!
What the?!
P-Please give me some pointers, goldfish pro!
The trick is...
to erase any hint of your presence
and swiftly strike the target from behind.
I see!
Put more flex into it,
from your wrist to your fingertips.
Okay!
You're a lucky girl.
You have a nice big sister looking after you.
Aren't I?
Katsuda's Sauce
Ka...
Katsuda's... Sauce...
Wow, it's really here!
Isn't that great, Ms. Yuki?
Here ya go!
Katsuda's Sauce
Sauce... Yummy...
The sauce is... yummy!
She's like a squirrel!
I like the way you're enjoying it, Miss.
It makes me happy.
Here, have another on me!
Sauce Senbei
500 yen
Wait, wait! I'll go buy a drink for you!
Riko?!
Don't worry! I'll be right back!
Jeez...
If we move around, I feel like
we'll lose each other even more,
so let's just wait over there for her.
I didn't know festivals were like this.
Ms. Yuki, you've never been
to a festival before?
Not exactly.
To me, the day of a festival meant...
Whoa...
So pretty!
Here you go, Ms. Yuki!
Ramune
Summer festivals are the best, aren't they?
Yes...
Whoa! Oh, man...
What are you doing?
You shook it, didn't you?
I'm so satisfied!
We even got to buy some sauce senbei
as a souvenir, too! Right?!
Yes.
But...
If I recall correctly,
you've already eaten eight of them,
Ms. Yuki's data
* Sauce Senbei: 8
* Ramune:
so hold off on having any more today!
Yes, ma'am...
I'm not sure who's the big sister anymore...
You're in my way! Move!
Someone! Please catch that man!
He stole my bag!
Riko! Ms. Yuki! Watch out!
Huh?
Are you okay?!
What's wrong?!
Did you hurt yourself somewhere...
Th-This is the first time anyone
besides Dad carried me like a princess...
I'm glad you seem okay.
Oh... Ms. Yuki's sauce senbei...
This is terrible...
Seriously, bad people like him
should receive divine punishment!
Divine... punishment?
On top of stealing, he almost killed someone.
It's normal to think that way.
Understood.
Huh?
M-Ms. Yuki?!
Oh, man, there she goes...
Big Brother! We have to go after Ms. Yuki!
Yeah... I'm worried about her.
My diary won't be complete without an
account of Ms. Yuki shanking an evildoer!
Don't say something like that...
Heh, piece of cake.
I see Ms. Yuki!
She's amazing! Ms. Yuki is like a superhero!
This isn't the time!
Big Brother, if we go this way,
we might be able to meet up with her!
All right!
If she causes an incident
out in the open like this...
D-Damn it!
Ms. Yuki!
Don't kill him!
This is divine punishment.
Master Hitoyoshi...
Being normal certainly makes my stomach growl.
You want to go buy more sauce senbei?
Yay! I'm gonna have some, too!
Didn't you say to hold off for today?
That doesn't apply to me!
That's him! The snatcher!
Hey, you! I'm going to have to ask you
to come with me to the station.
Come on. I said I'll be fine.
I can go home by myself.
Absolutely not. It's late, and way
too many things happened today.
It's late because so many
things happened today.
You've got it all backwards!
Just wait 'til I tell everyone what happened!
They'll be blown away!
"Everyone"...
This ended up being the best
research assignment ever!
Are these "research assignments"
something that everyone does, as well?
Yep, that's right.
Have you ever been to school before, Ms. Yuki?
School?
Yeah! You study, and chitchat
with friends, and join clubs!
School is a super fun place!
Wow! Beef stew?!
Mom
I'll have Big Brother
take me home, okay?
Take care.
We're having beef stew tonight.
I'm suddenly super hungry!
I wanna head home in a flash!
Hey!
Hurry up, Big Brother!
Jeez, she comes and goes like a whirlwind.
Seriously...
Yes. But she's a lot of fun to be around.
I guess it's okay, then.
Hey!
Is that... what "normal"...
looks like?
If that's the case,
I want to go to school, too.
Come to think of it, I never asked
how old Ms. Yuki is.
Yeah, if you want to make friends and stuff,
going to school might work.
Why not give it a try?
And before I knew it, that storm-like
August had already swept through,
and the new semester had begun.
I hope Ms. Yuki will be all right on her own...
Hey! Hitoyoshi!
Did you hear the rumors?!
Rumors?
Yeah!
There've been sightings of a super
pretty maid appearing around town!
Aw, gross!
My bad...
Well, she does stand out.
And even after the summer festival,
she often went for walks with Riko, too...
Oh, yeah? I didn't know.
Ha! I win!
Well, I've never seen her in person, but...
I saw her at the library.
For a cosplay, she really went all out with it.
The library?
All right, everyone take your seats!
Why was she at the library?
Well, at least no one's found out
about her living at my place...
Rich Flavor
Milk
I don't want to kick off the new semester with a bombardment of questions,
so I think I'll keep it on the down low...
I know this is sudden, but I have a new
transfer student to introduce to you all.
Yuki Yokoya
I am Yuki Yokoya.
Please call me Yuki.
Rich Flavor
Made from 100% Milk